Social media's philosophers
claim that age is just a number.
But most don't realize
that the moment you go from 17 to 18,
life smacks you in the face with adulting.
From the outside,
I look like the poster princess
of privilege and entitlement.
So why bother looking inside?
You've judged me already.
I am Pia Jaisingh.
Welcome to my roller coaster journey
with a hot guy and a lot of lies.
This is the Jaisingh clan.
That's my mom, Neelu Jaisingh.
- Has Rajat left, or is he still here?
- He's left.
And this is Dhanraj Jaisingh, my grandpa.
Piu! Have your breakfast at least
before you leave.
Morning, Grandpa.
What's the big hurry?
It's not as if you're headed
to take over Jaisingh & Sons.
If sarcasm was an Olympic sport,
- he'd be sure to bring home the gold.
- Have this.
- Thankfully…
- I'm going, baby.
…I only have to endure him
on the weekends.
LOVE WITH A SPRINKLING OF PATRIARCHY
From Monday to Friday,
I live in school. Falcon High.
From our lack of uniforms
and resort-type vibes,
you must have already figured out
that this is an ultra-elite school
where all the most pampered
and spoiled kids in Delhi come to study.
Their therapy bills are probably higher
than their school fees.
Falcon! Falcon!
And this is Falcon High's main character,
our principal and Delhi's Dumbledore,
Mrs Braganza Malhotra.
She sets the hearts of uncles aflutter
even today.
Ms Braganza!
Falconites.
New year, new semester.
New friendships, new enemies.
Live, love, laugh, fly, my birdies.
But! But, but, but!
If you try flying about
in these corridors,
you will answer to me,
if you know what I mean.
Especially the naïve birds of Grade 12
living out their final year.
You watch it!
And now LRI.
"LRI"?
"Let's rock it!"
I wish you a great year ahead, darlings.
Be wise with your choices,
be smart with your classes,
and be free with your clothes.
Take care.
Joy and kisses.
Rhea! Sahira!
- I missed you guys.
- Did you?
Come on, guys, I'm really sorry.
That stuff that happened on Bonfire Night?
It was all a huge misunderstanding.
And then Mom and I left immediately
for the retreat and
you know phones weren't allowed.
But I just got back from Europe yesterday
and I messaged you both.
Can't we talk it out and solve it?
Seems you spent the whole summer
practising excuses.
We are not interested, Pia.
Sahira…
- Rhea, please, just hear me out.
- Rhea!
To understand this world war,
let's go back a little in history.
Please sort this out, girl.
Rhea, Sahira, and I were BFFs
even before we could write ABC.
Our blood is definitely different,
but maybe our DNA is the same.
My whole childhood was a sisterhood.
They were actually beyond my best friends.
They were my
"home sweet home" feeling.
Until…
Yo, P!
Say hi at least.
- Let me go, Ayaan.
- What let go? Come here.
Hey!
- I got your birthday invitation.
- Already?
Yes, your mom texted me and she said
you'd invite me yourself too, yeah?
I have the perfect birthday gift
for you and your mom.
Gift for Mom? What?
What the heck are you doing, Ayaan?
You, come here.
- It's me, Ayaan Nanda.
- Oh my God!
Hey, hey, hey, P, wait. Look at us.
Pia Jaisingh, Ayaan Nanda.
Do you not like the ring of it?
Pia Jaisingh Nanda.
I knew it. I just knew it!
- Knew what?
- What are you doing?
I was on your side the whole of summer
but you are still...
Great, Sahira and Rhea are also here.
Let's just tell everybody today.
- Tell them what, Ayaan?
- How long has it been going on for?
- Since Bonfire Night. Remember...
- Bonfire Night?
Which means you lied to us. That's why
you didn't come to Bonfire Night.
It all makes sense now.
Guys, it's impossible that there would
ever be anything between Ayaan and me.
- What do you mean, impossible?
- What are you saying, P?
- I don't understand you anymore, Pia.
- P, I don't understand.
- You know how stupid I feel?
- Oh, Pia, you were always…
That's nonsense.
What are you talking about?
I mean, look at me.
What are you even talking about?
Pia, say something. Just try.
Just say something. Anything!
Because I already have a boyfriend!
- What?!
Liar, liar, pants on fire.
I have a boyfriend.
Who is it?
It's too new.
I don't want to jinx it
by saying something now.
You know how much
I believe in the evil eye.
That's why I haven't posted anything.
But he's good-looking, he's funny,
and smart enough to win "Who Wants
To Be A Millionaire" every year.
P, first, you hid
Ayaan's messages from us.
And now you're hiding your boyfriend?
Hiding things from us is not cool, P.
One second.
Even your besties don't know about it?
I'm calling bullshit.
I just told you,
we haven't gone public yet.
Public? Since when
did we become public, P?
What's up, guys? First day of school.
By the way, what's gone public?
How can it go public, Veer?
Pia is dating a guy
who doesn't want to be seen with her.
Maybe he's ugly. P's always had
a thing for charity since childhood.
Come on, guys.
I'm not in such dire straits
that I'd create an imaginary boyfriend.
He's real.
And very soon,
you'll see him on my grid as well.
Happy?
We'll be happy when you stop
hiding the truth from us, Pia.
Let's go, Rhea.
Your boyfriend, huh? All bullshit.
Shit, shit, shit!
Now where will I find this fake boyfriend?
Cool, good-looking, smart, and romantic?
No human male can be all that!
Terrible idea!
Terrible, terrible, terrible!
Actually, it's not such a bad idea.
Red flag!
Massive red flag!
Hi.
Red… flag?
I know, at such short notice,
I won't be able to find
a guy with a six-pack
who's also smart and handsome.
But there must be somebody
who can play the hero of my rom-com…
sorry, my rom-con?
The sight of whom
makes every dating app freeze.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Ma.
- New goal unlocked.
- Well done.
I don't get it.
We're in the same city, so why do you
want to go to boarding school?
We've had this discussion 100 times, guys.
Can't we ride to school together
like always?
Yes! And anyway,
you have to leave next year, right?
Exactly!
Let's start practicing from today.
And who will take care
of your strict diet there?
Who will make smoothies for you there?
Nobody will do it. Thank God!
I love you, guys.
Okay, today is my first day of school.
I don't want to be late.
Give me one chance, guys.
I have to stay alone.
God, how fast they grow up.
He was a little boy not so long ago.
I told you that
we should have another baby.
Really?
The idea is quite interesting.
I like it. Don't change your mind now.
When you're voting for
the debate team captain, remember this.
There's a lot more
where that's come from, guys.
Goenka!
When you have to resort to bribery
in your campaign,
it means only one thing.
The leader is not strong enough.
Ah, there he is. Arjun.
Our new scholarship student
who has joined us for our last year.
From Noida. Greater Noida, I mean.
Greatest Noida.
I'm not ashamed
that I come from Noida, Aakash.
So, try harder.
You all saw that? So cute.
Noida pride and all, Mehra?
It's Mehta.
Whatever, bro.
You may have won a lot of debates
at your "greatest" Noida's
shitty, tier-two school.
But this? This is
the International Debate Championship.
The winner gets direct entry
into the Ivy League.
My dad went to an Ivy League university.
My grandpa went to
an Ivy League university.
And I will also go to one.
Because this is a family tradition
of us Goenkas.
Tell me something.
What's the legacy of you Mehras?
I've never heard of it.
Is it some government degree college
from Ghaziabad or Faridabad?
Before what little respect you have left
is ripped to shreds,
withdraw your name from the captaincy.
Mehra!
- Goenka!
Are you done? Or is there more?
I'm glad you got personal, Aakash.
Because now I can ethically kick your ass.
So, listen, Goyal.
- It's Goenka.
- Whatever, bro.
My father is a doctor.
He studied in Ghaziabad.
But today, he treats your father.
My mother is a teacher.
She got her degree in Faridabad.
But today, she teaches you.
I too studied in Noida before this.
But there, we didn't have losers like you.
So just to be able to feel
a superiority complex,
I had to get transferred here.
My name is Arjun Mehta.
M-E-H-T-A. Mehta.
You'd better say it with respect.
Because I am the next captain
of this debate team.
And you, you're that flunkie
whose girlfriend dates him
only for the new iPhone.
- Arjun!
Who do you guys think
should lead you all into battle?
This massive little dimwit of a clown?
Or me?
- Arjun!
Aakash… who is that?
Arjun Mehr… Mehta.
Mrs Mehta's son.
This is the first time
I've seen somebody win in the debate team
by showing his body off.
He's a new student.
Good-looking. Swimming champion.
No social media presence
so nobody will be able to trace him.
Green flags all over.
Potential.
Thank you, universe.
I'll handle it from here.
Thank you, brother. See you.
See you tomorrow.
Come on, man. Let him be.
Let me go!
- Why did you throw my note away?
- Who are you?
- I'm Pia Jaisingh.
- Who?
Don't pretend you don't recognise me.
I have three lakh followers.
- India has a huge population.
- Who do you think you are?
- Dude...
- Arjun!
- Where were you, son?
- Ma?
I've been looking for you.
Why aren't you answering Papa's calls?
Okay, listen. I've cooked
your favourite gobidish.
Take it from the lunch room.
Ma, I'm coming home
on the weekend. I'll eat it then.
Okay, listen, but you must have
a lot of dirty laundry.
- Four pairs of underwear a day...
- Ma!
Actually, I've promised Pia
that I'll help her
with the science project.
We're getting late, right, Pia?
No! Ma'am was asking about
your underwear, right?
Tell her...
I'm running late,
and both of you should get to class.
Perfect. Bye, Mom.
Hey, listen to me. Arjun!
Why are you chasing me?
Will you come to my birthday as my date?
What?
I don't understand.
What don't you understand?
Anything.
That's strange.
Your mom's a teacher
and your dad's a doctor.
And the genes for smarts skipped you?
Very funny. Bye.
Arjun!
Come on, dude. Please listen to me
for two minutes at least.
I don't want you to be a real date.
I just need you to pretend to be my date.
But why?
Why do you want to go
with a random guy on your own birthday?
Do you have the time for
"Once upon a time…"?
Absolutely not!
Arjun, please, please, please!
You're my last hope.
Please, please, please?
If you listen, you'll understand.
Seems to me you won't let me go
until you've told me. Right?
So…
You may find all of this TMI,
but I think that to convince you,
I'll have to start from the beginning.
Birthdays were always special to me.
Because it was the one day
when I felt the most loved by my family.
Don't get me wrong.
I was the apple of their eye.
But growing up, I felt that
Mom and Dad always wanted a son.
- And they kept trying but…
- It didn't work.
Hello?
Mommy? Momma!
They fought every day
and grew further and further apart.
- I need peace too.
- And you've got it!
You got it too.
Hello?
Hey.
Papa became the hot topic
of kitty parties in Delhi.
- What difference does it make?
- And Mom grew increasingly lonely.
But she wasn't the only one
who felt lonely.
But Rhea and Sahira?
They never left my side.
We became each other's chosen family.
But this family too got jinxed.
Come on, guys.
Why do you always do this to me?
Don't blame us
for your own stuff-up, Rhee.
You guys are always
laughing at me. I'm really upset.
P, is it necessary that you leave today?
It's the last day of school
and it's also Bonfire Night.
Can't you talk to Neelu Aunty?
I'm sure she'll understand.
I'm going to complain to Aunty.
What kind of retreat is this
where phones are not allowed?
Guys, I have to do this for Mom.
She's finally taking a step for herself
to get better,
and this retreat is very important
for her mental health and peace.
I just have to go.
We get it. Come on.
This was a good take.
I look so funny.
You guys always pick the take
where I'm not...
But you look so pretty!
It's a message from Ayaan.
Yo, P, am I seeing you tonight?
Pia, what's this?
Sahira, I don't know why
he's sending me such messages.
Look, I haven't even replied.
One second, scroll up.
You haven't replied, but you didn't stop
him either, did you?
Pia, what does all this mean?
Ayaan and you...
It's nothing.
Ayaan's been randomly
messaging you for two weeks,
and you didn't tell me about this
even once?
You know how I've felt about Ayaan
since we were kids.
And you still did that?
You call yourself my sister?
Sisters don't do this.
I wouldn't even dream
of doing such a thing to you.
- Let's go, Rhea.
- Sahira…
Sahira!
Pia, what you did is terrible.
It's just not done!
And after the summer holidays,
when I came to school,
everyone confronted me
on the first day itself.
And in desperation, I had to tell this lie
that I have a boyfriend.
So, your childhood best friend,
sorry, sister,
thinks that you are stealing
her lifelong crush.
- What kind of friendship is this?
- I myself am confused.
I had no idea that anyone would make
such a mountain out of a molehill.
Of course,
unless there's some truth to it.
- You...
- Ow!
Are you crazy?
I didn't tell Sahira about Ayaan because
I didn't want to hurt her feelings.
Sahira has liked him since she was little.
Just to protect her
I had to tell this little lie,
and everything went wrong.
That's why I need a boyfriend
just for a few days.
Albeit a fake one.
Then Sahira will realise that
I have no interest in Ayaan,
Rhea will also forgive me,
and all my problems will be solved.
Of course they will be. What about me?
You get to be on my grid.
Your grid? Oh my God!
Not interested.
I'll pay you.
10,000 a week. Flat fee.
10,000 a week?
How many weeks' plan is this?
I'm sorry, I'm very busy.
Please. I'm out.
Just a couple of weeks, man.
For now, let's shake on this deal.
QUICK LAW
25K per week.
What? No, man!
- Well then, sorry, Pia. No deal.
- Hey! Arjun!
Arjun, please.
Don't you feel ashamed,
ripping a girl off like this?
- Not at all.
- Okay, fine. Deal.
Deal.
Now what's the plan?
You have to go!
Okay.
I want poses like these.
No, no, no, no!
The guys at school
cannot see me in such idiotic poses, Pia.
They won't see them.
It's just for the soft launch.
We'll take photos sneakily.
Your face won't be visible.
But the whole school will wonder,
who's this mystery boy with Pia?
And then, boom!
On my birthday will be the big reveal.
You know how you watch the trailer
before the film?
Just like that.
When and where?
You'll receive the details.
- Hey, what's up?
- Where have you been?
I've been calling you since forever.
My highlighter's losing its glow.
There's a little too much glow.
You look like a frying pan.
My phone is usually on silent. Unlike you.
Anyway,
was this boring location the only place
you could find for the photos?
I mean, just look at these walls.
Let's go.
You don't know
the value of elevator selfies.
Elevator selfie?
I thought we'd take it in a more,
you know, aesthetically pleasing place.
Like with grass, flowers,
and maybe the moon can be out.
You know, maybe like, nice twilight…
Happy?
Come on, come closer.
- What?
- Come closer.
Closer.
Even more.
- Arjun?
- Yeah?
Is your name Arjun McShy?
It's Mehta. You know that.
Then why are you so shy?
Have you never held a girl's hand before?
Of course I have.
Then put your hands on my waist,
for God's sake.
Hide your face.
Hey! Did you see the post?
Hey! Isn't this Pia?
Pia has a secret boyfriend?
Do you think it's Rudra?
Minions, start the background checks.
I pay you guys way too much
to do way too little.
I'll just do it myself!
Oh my God! Pia. Well done.
Tell me who this mystery guy is.
I can't reveal.
Wait, I'll find out.
OUCH FOR AYAAN LOL
WHERE SHOULD I MEET YOU?
#BLACKSPECSGOALS
Hashtag KUWK.
"Keeping up with dark glasses."
This means she wasn't lying.
Didn't I tell you?
Pia would never do that to you.
Pia, we forgive you.
Why didn't you tell us
you had a boyfriend?
- We'd never have had the misunderstanding.
- I'm sorry, I should've said.
Yeah, P, of course, I forgive you, girl.
Come here.
You have a boyfriend. Obviously,
there couldn't be anything happening.
Of course. I have a boyfriend.
- Who is this guy?
- Where did you meet?
He's not a junior, I hope.
I was telling her...
Mercury is in retrograde.
So I cannot share
any good news until my birthday.
You know stalking is my number one talent.
You know I'll find out.
SHOW HIS FACE, MAN
Thank you.
Got it. And upload.
Why is your wallpaper 11:11?
Actually, one can't see falling stars
because of pollution, right?
So 11:11 is that shooting star.
Whenever you see it, you make a wish.
Come, let me show you.
Give me your hands.
Shut your eyes.
- And make a wish.
- Okay.
I wish…
What did you wish for?
Nothing.
Actually, I wished
that gazing at my hotness
shouldn't make your intentions naughty.
Oh, really?
Actually, I also asked for the same thing.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Shall I tell you the truth?
Go on.
- Shall I?
- Yes.
You are so hot
that maybe you are the real cause
of global warming.
- But Pia…
- Yes?
You're to blame
for the melting ice in Kashmir
and the poor rainfall in Mumbai.
Hence, you are cancelled.
You! I'll cancel you!
Chill. Anyway, you're not my type. Stupid.
I'm much smarter than you,
you walking, talking science textbook!
Mom?
Hello?
Hello? Pia?
I saw your photos with that boy
on social media.
You're all over him.
Grandma was so embarrassed.
Which photos, Mom?
The photos were all normal.
Who is this boy?
I hope he's of our status
and from a good family.
You won't know him.
But he must surely have a name.
It's a surprise, Mom. You'll meet him
tomorrow at the birthday party.
I'll introduce you.
- I hate surprises!
- There's no network. I'll call you later.
- Bye.
- Hello?!
Pia, this is not funny.
How can you kidnap me like this?
What's next? Are you going to
demand a ransom? Pia!
- Come on!
- Why do you always overreact so much?
This was the only way
to get you inside undetected.
What the…?
People are waiting. It's getting late,
and here you are being dramatic.
What?
Happy birthday, Pia.
Thanks.
By the way, I look good
in this rented suit too, right?
"Too"?
So, you think I look nice.
Back-handed compliment.
Nice.
Okay.
This is it.
Everybody will be convinced
that we are in love, right?
Yes. Absolutely!
- Hi.
- Look, Veer!
- Hi, Pia!
- What's up?
- Happy birthday.
- Hi!
Hi. Arjun.
- Nice to finally see you.
- You too.
- Great job landing P.
- Thank you.
- Arjun, Sahira.
- Hi.
Hi, how are you?
Come.
He is so hot.
- Oh my God!
- Hi, Piu.
Who is this dude?
When we didn't find anyone in school,
I was sure she would turn up with Rudra.
Rudra is not in India at the moment.
Anyway, he's from our school.
But I haven't seen him before
in our school.
Whatever. They look really good together.
- I know.
- They make such a cute couple.
Pia's boyfriend looks like a prince.
Yes, he has princely vibes.
Seems like he's from the royal family
of Jaisalmer or something.
And you were worried about the family.
He's almost royalty.
I don't want "almost".
I want a real prince for my Pia.
Rudra is five years older than Pia.
Delhi's prince, Ayaan, is also available.
Come on, she's too young.
Hi.
- My baby, happy birthday.
- Happy birthday.
Mom, Dad, this is Arjun, my boyfriend.
- Hi, ma'am.
- Hello.
Hi, sir.
Arjun has caused ripples
from the day he joined this school.
He became the captain of the debate team.
He's a national-level swimmer
and a class topper too.
- That's impressive. Congratulations.
- Thank you, sir.
- Guys, come on. Let's dance. Come on.
- Sorry, Uncle.
- Come on, guys. We have to dance.
- No.
- No? Why?
- Guys, Arjun does not dance.
Why not? It's your 18th birthday.
Of course, he'll dance. Right, Arjun?
Arjun, can't you do
even this much for Pia?
Can he even dance?
One second, Pia.
Today, for the first time in years,
I feel like believing in
the magic of birthday candles.
And I have only one wish to ask for.
I wish time would stop
and everything would remain as it is.
Pia?!
- Oh. Hi, life.
- Pia!
Arjun's papa, Dr Mehta, is on the phone.
Child, you came here
all the way from Noida.
He's worried.
You should have called him.
- Here, speak to him.
- Is this Dr Mehta's son?
- Isn't he their family doctor?
- Really?
This was your surprise?
- Yes, Papa?
- Why is your phone on silent?
He doesn't belong to our class.
Is this the way you embarrass me?
What are you doing at the Jaisinghs' home?
Just wait there. I'll pick you up.
- He's not even from a business family.
- You're a Jaisingh. Remember that.
I knew it. Not prince,
but peasant is her type.
Neelu Aunty's worst nightmare.
I feel so bad for her.
Best party ever. I am so glad I came.
Looks like Arjun found a sugar mommy.
Why don't you tell me anything
these days, man?
Papa, I'm coming. I'll come on my own.
Listen. Arjun...
- Papa, I'm coming, okay?
- Hello?
- He's not so rich, I guess.
- Come now... Hello?
Pia could have done way better, babe.
Why has the party stopped, man?
Yes, buddy, keep heading this way.
Just look for the location, man.
- Arjun!
- Yes, that swanky mansion.
- Arjun, please, I'm really sorry.
- Yes.
None of that was meant to happen.
You should have informed me
that the 25,000
included insulting me and my family too.
My ride's here. I've got to go.
No! Arjun, please come back inside.
- Please, I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
- Let go. Let me go.
- Arjun, no. Please. Please, don't go.
- Pia, stop. Okay.
- Arjun, I'm very strong. I won't let go.
- I'm so sorry, buddy.
Just two minutes. This girl is indulging
in a bit of Adam-teasing.
I'll deal with it and come right back.
Brother… I can empathise.
My betrothed also likes to argue.
Betrothed? What?
God! Arjun, I'm really sorry.
Mom's intention was not to insult you.
When it comes to me, she forgets
what's right and what's wrong.
Am I right or wrong?
You are 100% right!
Don't lose your confidence.
Stand firm for your love.
Bro, please listen.
Madam, no "bro". Only Govardhan, please.
Arjun, can't we go inside and talk?
I don't have time for this shit, man!
- Govardhan, open…
- Oh, no.
- Govardhan!
- No, bro, why are you getting so agitated?
You see, at the root of all love
lies fighting.
And at the root of every fight is love.
So please enjoy both these things.
Don't worry about a taxi.
If one goes, another will come.
Please see this through all the way first.
- Okay, madam, bye.
- Bye.
Govardhan, where are you going?
Stop. Shit!
- Drive safe, Mr Govardhan.
- Come back!
You see? Even Mr Govardhan believed
that our fake relationship is real.
You make a very good fake boyfriend.
Ex-boyfriend.
Tonight, at 12:00 p.m., this carrot
will turn into a pumpkin, Cinderella.
Your contract is over.
Actually, there's still two minutes left.
- Shit. Pia, is that your dad?
- Don't worry.
- I got this. It's okay.
- Shit, what must he think?
- Just be calm. It's fine.
- I'm screwed. He's coming here.
- Dad, I...
- Piu! I am not talking to you.
I've seen this in films.
Rich dads carry rifles.
If you touch the daughter, shoot.
Fortunately,
I don't even have a gun.
What are you doing on Saturday night?
Me?
Dinner with the family?
Let's get to know each other.
Sure, sir.
You will have dinner at home?
Yes. Why? No? You don't want me to?
Sorry, Piu. I'll have to go.
Some delegates are visiting.
Yes? Take care.
- Good night, sir.
- Yes, you come with me.
I'll drop you home.
- It's fine.
- Bye, Piu. He says bye.
Bye.
Help.
Arjun… Arjun!
Get up, man! Wake up!
- Arjun!
- Pia?
What the… What are you doing here?
I'm a witch.
I'm here to ruin your sleep.
Shit, Pia. What are you doing here?
Couldn't you call up?
Actually, my phone is on silent. I...
Listen to me first.
Could you please renew your services?
- On a weekly basis.
- What?
How much money do you want to waste?
It's only money.
No cost is too great to keep Papa at home.
Because of you,
we will finally have dinner with Papa
together as a family.
I don't know how many months
or years it's been.
Your dad, by the way, is very cool.
We had a great chat in the car.
About what?
Next year's predictions.
Fiscal deficits. Budgets.
Of course, that makes sense.
Discussing fiscal deficits over dinner
sounds like his absolute dream.
That's why he always wanted a son.
Why? Can't girls discuss that?
Of course they can.
But…
But I'm not sure if I can or not.
Why do you always
doubt yourself so much, Pia?
You know…
In my house,
nobody ever took me seriously.
And in my home,
everything is taken a bit too seriously.
That's why I take you seriously.
Services extended.
For you, 80%, 90, 100% discount.
We underestimate it so much, this feeling
of having someone who takes us seriously.
Who views our problems as their problems.
I hired Arjun
to save my family of friends.
But now it feels like he could end up
saving my real family.
Look, now we're going public.
Not only online,
but in reality also,
we'll have to convince everybody
that we are in love.
So…
Now, a robot is going to tell us
what real people do in love?
People in love express their affection
using their love languages.
One, gifts giving.
As in materialistic happiness.
Two, acts of service.
As in devotional, selfless happiness.
Three, words of affirmation.
As in the happiness of sugar-coated words.
Four, quality time.
As in, just Netflix and no chill.
Five, physical touch.
Just chill and no Netflix.
Obviously, physical touch is out.
What? Why?
Because I'm not your type at all. Right?
It's okay.
It's squid-ink pasta.
- Try it.
- Yes, Aunty. I mean, ma'am.
So Arjun, the captain of the
International Debate Championship team.
Very impressive.
And if you win there,
the world's best colleges
will lay out the red carpet for you.
- Right?
- Yes sir.
But my eyes are focused
only on a law school scholarship.
Dad also studied law
at an Ivy League university.
Yes, that was a long time ago.
I always wished that my son
would follow in my footsteps.
Graduate from an Ivy League college.
But I guess God had other plans.
Gave me a gorgeous little daughter.
Cute little daughter. Right?
Sir, Pia could do it too.
Of course. But those colleges
don't offer degrees in fashion design,
or being a pastry chef.
Unless you have plans again.
Rajat, we should rename our law firm
to Jaisingh & Daughters.
What do you say, Pia?
You guys are treating this as a joke.
Pia, I think you'd make a great lawyer.
She looks very sweet,
but her brain is
as sharp as a razor blade.
If she reads something,
she remembers it forever.
Her logic and argumentative skills
are so sharp
that I'm actually quite happy
she's not interested in law.
Otherwise, who knows?
She might defeat me
and become the captain of the debate team.
Piu, is that right? What?
If you don't mind me saying, sir,
sometimes, we underestimate
those closest to us.
We are not able
to judge their calibre aptly.
After being close to Pia,
I have seen her true potential.
And who knows?
She could become the world's best lawyer.
We were having dinner with Arjun,
that's why.
Yeah, see you.
- Hi.
- Has Arjun left?
- Yes, he just left.
Listen, why don't you join
the debate team with Arjun?
I feel like I'm already
on the debate team.
I spend so much time with him
that sometimes,
I end up practicing with him.
And what did you discuss
in the last session?
The debate was about the morality
of private healthcare.
Should vaccines be sold during a pandemic
or should they be distributed freely?
- And were you...
- And...
Sorry, go ahead.
And were you "for" or "against"?
- Arjun was "against" but I was "for".
- You were for, really?
It would be easier to argue "against".
You'd get moral brownie points.
Anyway, what was your argument?
Hot chocolate?
A little bit.
- If you make it.
- Okay.
I wanted a challenge.
So, I said the raw materials
for the vaccines cost money.
Syringes and serums
obviously don't grow on trees.
Not to mention the compensation
deserved by the scientists
who spent entire lifetimes
finding and giving us the cure
to this virus so quickly.
So, if the government or a charitable
institution can bear the cost of this,
then we can
distribute the vaccines to the public.
Otherwise, pharmaceutical companies
will go bankrupt
and nobody will try to find the cure
to anything ever again.
Honestly, it's really
the only sustainable way
to fund incentivised
scientific develop… ment.
What?
Was that my baby princess arguing there?
How good were you!
Look at the way you argued.
You kept it so balanced and nuanced.
You know, join the debate team.
I see a young, budding lawyer.
- Really?
- Really.
It's in your blood.
Don't you think Grandpa said
a sensible thing for the first time today?
It's time to change the name
of Jaisingh & Sons.
Sir?
Sorry, tell the driver to leave.
Yes? Thank you.
Papa's going to stay home tonight.
Yay! I'm excited!
My princess! So proud of you.
- Arjun, come out!
- Have you lost your mind?
I have to join the debate team somehow.
Only you can help me.
Joining the debate team
isn't some joke Pia.
You need to be focused and work hard.
It shouldn't be that while training you,
I get distracted from my own goals.
And your attention span. My God!
It's no longer than a reel.
- How can you...
- I thought you believed in me.
You said something else
at dinner yesterday.
Yes, I was lying.
Just like our relationship.
You…
Arjun!
Mama, once, just once, if you knock
before coming in, I'll just faint.
Be respectful when you talk to me.
And also with Pia.
Actually, ma'am,
maybe Arjun is right.
I'll never be able
to join the debate team.
Pia, you're no less capable
than anyone else.
You can do whatever you please.
Arjun, you will train Pia. That's final.
The International Debate Championship
is in just two months, Ma. How?
You have a whole two months.
By the way,
how much will you keep lifting?
The girls clearly don't care.
Not "girls", bro.
The girl doesn't seem to care.
But don't forget,
the Nandas always get what they want.
Watches, cars, girls.
I'll get Pia too.
Arjun is a nobody.
Ayaan, we're living in 2024.
Let go of this toxic mindset.
There's a huge difference
between girls and cars.
Don't lose what you already have.
Just focus on Sahira.
Why focus on Sahira, bro?
She's not going anywhere.
I just need to kick Arjun's ass.
- Hi, P!
- Hi!
- You're looking so good!
- Cheers, babe!
- Come, sit.
- What's up Arjun?
- Hi, P!
- Hi, Pia.
- Hey!
- Hi.
First of all,
welcome to the family, Arjun.
- Thank you, guys.
- Welcome, Arjun.
And guys, there's one more piece of news.
That Ayaan and I
are finally, officially dating.
I knew it. This was just meant to happen.
But I mean, come on, guys.
When did this happen?
You never told us.
- Really?
- I thought I'd tell you today.
Excuse me, sir. Still or sparkling water?
No bottled water. Regular water, please.
- That's all.
- We only serve bottled water, sir.
Well, in that case, room temperature water
for me and for Pia…
For me, one...
Sparkling water, four cubes of ice,
a drizzle of lime, and some sea salt.
Wow.
Instead of going into so much detail,
isn't it better to just order a mocktail?
Tacky, Arjun.
You should know Pia's taste.
I mean, we all admit that
her taste is a little bad.
We don't judge. Do we?
Guys, what difference does all this make?
Sparkling, still, who cares?
What matters is,
Arjun is now dating our best friend,
and we still don't know anything
about Arjun.
True.
Why delay?
Tell us everything about yourself.
Yes, tell us everything.
You can open up to us. It's a safe space.
I'm an open book.
Mom's a teacher. Dad is a doctor.
We live together in Noida.
Not Noida, bro, "Nyodda".
So Arjun, what brought you to Falcon High?
100% scholarship.
Wow!
- That's very impressive.
- Smart.
There were a couple of options,
but since Mom works here,
we chose Falcon High.
Chose? You?
You must have topped
the school's charity initiatives list.
Isn't that how you got in? No?
Seriously, Ayaan?
I'm just kidding, man.
He's a debate champion.
Arjun, surely you're on social media?
You have some page or something?
We tried so hard to stalk you,
but we couldn't find anything.
So, Arjun, tell me something.
Pia is so far out of your league,
how did you land her?
I know how he landed her, man.
There must be some competition
running in his village.
"How to land a girl in six days!"
Date, Dupe… Which is it?
Just channelling my inner "Nyodda" energy.
The last question is for all of you.
Let's not target Arjun, guys.
It's been too much.
Whoever answers this question
gets a free shot on me.
The question is this.
Do you think
Arjun Mehta deserves Pia Jaisingh?
Or just like the school,
is Pia also practising charity
out of pity?
Speak up. What's the answer?
Does this Prince of Noida
deserve our Pia or not?
- Does he deserve her, Sahira?
- Shut the hell up, Ayaan!
That's enough!
Who the hell are you to say anything?
And how can you say such idiotic things?
In this day and age, you show so much
classism and elitism through humour?
I feel sorry for you.
And now,
listen to me carefully, all of you!
This is the last time that you will
get away with insulting Arjun.
If this ever happens again,
then our gang will be broken forever.
Are we clear?
Good.
Let's go, Arjun.
- Listen, say sorry. Say sorry.
- Why, man?
Let's go, Arjun!
Pia, girl, please…
I hope I didn't say too much in anger.
Papa says
that when your anger's too hot to control,
you should eat an ice cream.
But not just one. At least two.
It helps you calm down.
You need three, I think.
Okay, tell me something.
Would you really stop talking
to your childhood friends for my sake?
In life, at some point or another,
you have to take a stand
for what is right.
Then it's time I took a stand for you too.
I will train you for the debate team, Pia.
Wow!
You'll put your goals aside to train me?
Why?
Because you're my first and only friend.
Look at you, my green flag.
You know, I've realised,
it doesn't matter
who you go to the biggest party with,
or who you're with
during your most heartbreaking moment.
All that really matters is,
five minutes after all that is over,
who is left standing by your side?
Look, we've been standing here
for the last 20 minutes.
Yeah.
And suddenly Arjun and I were not
fighting with each other
but for each other.
He was a fake boyfriend,
but I think we started
a real friendship that day.
What's the score?
I wasn't watching the match.
Oh?
Mrs Braganza is chasing me.
I have to submit my college application.
And where are you thinking of going?
Definitely London!
- Have you already applied?
- Of course.
National Law College.
Arjun.
Why are you applying here in Haryana
instead of the world's best colleges?
I know it's a very good university,
but an Ivy League
or Oxbridge education is life-changing.
You'll get a different level of exposure.
You don't understand.
I'll explain. Come.
Oh my God!
Arjun, what is this?
My vision board.
I agreed to fake-dating
because I'm saving money
for my dream app, Quick Law.
My swimming will provide me with a full
scholarship at National Law College.
I don't want Mom and Dad
to spend anything on my education.
So,
I'll top every semester.
I'll bag the best internship,
and in the final year,
through campus placement, I'll land a job.
There, I'll build my network
and earn money too.
And then, the main goal.
My passion project.
Quick Law.
An app that will connect the layman
to the best lawyers in the country.
Well, thank you.
After that, I'll get some VC funding.
And then I'll sell this app
to Google for millions.
Ma and Papa
will finally be able to retire.
They've both worked very hard
for many years, Pia.
I want to give them the best life.
Hmm…
What are you thinking about?
In this vision board,
friends, life,
and…
love
don't seem to have any space.
If you get any off-time
from your daily goals,
do think about it.
Okay, guys, here comes Pia Jaisingh!
- Pia, you're up.
- Come on, Pia. Come on!
Pia, what happened?
Are you scared? Should be.
Pia, listen to me.
If you stand up to bullies,
they back down.
Remember one thing.
People who degrade others are weak inside.
Pia. True victory is in never
backing down before them.
Come on, you got this.
Congratulations, Pia.
By the way, Sanjay is a very good cook.
The food looks amazing. Thank you so much.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
So, are you two just friends or, you know,
something more than that?
Papa! He's just joking.
You don't have to answer that.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay, Uncle.
Arjun… is my friend.
In fact, these days,
it feels like he is my best friend.
Unlike Arjun,
I've had a lot of friends since childhood.
But… I've never met anyone like Arjun.
He is still busy.
But now, in his timetable,
he makes some time for friends as well.
The thing is,
we are very protective of him.
Way too much!
He was born prematurely.
In the seventh month.
Sanjay was busy in the emergency ward.
I had to deliver him alone.
After that, we both decided that
we would not miss
a single moment of Arjun's life.
You both must have sacrificed
so much for Arjun.
It is not a sacrifice, child.
This is called parenting.
Children are the responsibility
of parents.
Arjun always comes first.
So now tell me,
what is the meaning of "IDK"?
Ma'am, "I don't know."
Even you don't know?
Who made you the prefect?
Ma'am, you did.
- Ma'am? Arjun.
- Hi, ma'am.
Oh, hello, Arjun, you're here.
Otherwise, I would have to TTYL.
"Talk to you later"
is not actually used in this context.
WTF
I sit here and continuously try to learn
the lingo but in spite of that…
Ma'am, did you just say "WTF"?
WTF. Wednesday, Thursday, Friday?
Anyway, Arjun,
today I have to talk to you,
especially about your future plans.
You've applied to National Law College
on the basis of a swimming scholarship.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm not considering going abroad, ma'am.
Arjun, if you're making this decision
because of money,
then I think you can win
this year's Albright Sports Scholarship.
- Albright Scholarship?
- Yes.
You can apply to any university in the UK.
And it's a full
three-year paid scholarship, Arjun.
All expenses paid.
Stay, food, drink.
Not that kind of drink, of course.
But you know what I mean.
There's no catch, Arjun.
I mean, India is great.
But I think that specifically for you,
the student programs there
would be better suited.
I can apply anywhere in the UK?
Of course, anywhere.
Where would you like to study?
London! Or anywhere close to London.
Okay, close to London. Okay.
So, my assistants
and the school's guidance counsellor
will be in touch with you about the,
you know, process of application and all.
And I look forward to reading your essay.
- LOL.
- LOL?
"Lots of love."
Now, FU.
"Finish Up."
The next student has to come in.
Right, okay.
Rudra called today.
He's coming over for Diwali too.
I know. He messaged me.
Mom, Ria and Sahira have already
zeroed down on their Diwali outfits.
I am the only one who hasn't.
Look at this. Gorgeous.
White? Are you sure it'll look good on me?
Gorgeous, as always.
All colours look good on you.
You know, before I got married,
when I was an interior designer
and your Papa and I were dating,
he loved me in white.
He used to say,
"Neelu, you look the prettiest."
- Mama?
- Yes?
Will you and Papa ever…?
I'd accepted things for what they were.
But now, I don't know why
I feel that once again…
Maybe…
Maybe we can become a family again?
- Hello, darling. Happy Diwali.
- Happy Diwali.
There you go.
- I'll have some too?
- Mom? Dad?
Oh wow! My son looks so handsome.
Okay listen, come back early.
Tomorrow morning, Mom, you, and Pia
have to leave for Mumbai
for the debate championship.
Of course, Dad. I'm never late.
- I hope I'm looking good.
- Of course.
You take after your father.
Of course you look good!
Pia will like it, right?
She will love it.
Now go, it's getting late.
Okay, bye.
- I'm coming, just wait. Sit down.
- Come, come! Come and join.
You look lovely.
- Hello, sir.
- For you...
Happy Diwali.
- Happy Diwali, sir. Thank you.
- Looking good.
- Happy Diwali, Aunty.
- Happy Diwali.
- Looking for Piu?
- Yes, sir.
- She's out there.
- Okay.
- Thank you, sir.
- Have fun.
You know what?
White always looks good on you.
Looks good.
Sahira, please call Arjun.
I left my phone in the room.
Piu, chill out. He must be on his way.
He's probably just, like,
fashionably late or something.
- Ah, hello! Hi, hi, hi. Hello!
- Hi, Arjun.
Where were you?
Why did you come so late, Arjun?
Be on time for once.
- Happy Diwali, Pia.
- Happy Diwali.
You look very happy.
And very beautiful too.
Wow! A direct compliment?
You're flirting with me, Mehta.
You know, people say
that Diwali
is the festival of new beginnings.
We've taken many fake photos.
Today, for the first time,
shall we take a real one?
This photo will be only for us.
Party all night. Don't be shy, just dance.
Go, Rudra!
Rudra is here.
Pia? It's getting late.
- The competition is tomorrow.
- No! Just stay!
- We have a flight tomorrow.
- Please, Arjun.
What?
Your own daughter has read the message!
What must she be thinking?
When did you think
you were going to tell us?
All this time, I was thinking that you had
some sort of midlife crisis going on!
That you'd get through it one day
and come back home.
But you have gone
and got that waitress pregnant!
Just shut up! Shut up!
I've had enough of you!
You don't know it all, okay?
Think before you speak!
You don't know anything about her!
She was there for me
when you were not there, Neelu!
If she had any shame, she wouldn't have
gotten involved with a married man!
I never told her that I was married!
The minute she got to know,
she wanted to break up!
But I love her, Neelu. I love her.
And I wasn't able to let her go.
You couldn't let her go?
But it was easy for you to let go
of your 24-year-long marriage?
I'm blaming her unnecessarily
when the fault is completely yours, Rajat!
The real mistake was our marriage.
And for Pia's sake,
stop screaming, please.
If you cared about your daughter at all,
you wouldn't let this family break up!
Stop screaming, please! Piu can hear!
You're the one screaming!
So what else can I do? Talking to you
without shouting is impossible.
I don't want to live
in this unhappy marriage, Rajat!
Walk out! Get out of my life!
You can walk out too!
No! You have walked out!
You broke my house.
And keep your accusations to yourself!
I told you many times that
we shouldn't try to have another child.
But no! You kept trying cycle
after cycle of IVF!
And then what? The same hope.
The same disappointment.
You never saw what you had.
You always kept running after
what you didn't have.
I kept running? You also kept running!
I was busy
working for the family, damn it!
Not for a son!
To this day, it is the Jaisingh family's
obsession to have a son.
Take Papa-ji, for instance.
Even today,
he uses sarcasm and silence
to remind me at least once every day
how I never gave you a son!
I'm not Dhanraj Jaisingh!
Get that in your head!
That's what you think, Papa.
Until two days ago, you also thought that
I couldn't become a lawyer, right?
That I couldn't take over
Jaisingh & Sons.
- It's not about you.
- No!
It's not about you, my child.
What is happening in this house?!
Will we ever be all right?
My child… try and understand.
Your mother tried really hard,
I tried really hard,
but sadly, we weren't able
to try hard together.
I don't think this is going to work.
Try to understand.
Divorce is the only option.
No!
No! No!
My child, everything will be all right.
You're going to marry her?
Piu, you know she's going to have a baby.
She's pregnant.
I can't leave her in this state.
It's not right.
Is it because you think it could be a boy?
- No, baby.
- No, Piu.
I blamed myself!
I kept thinking that
you two were fighting because of me!
I've waited my entire life
for your approval!
Enough! There have been
too many fights in this house.
Divorce is the right decision.
Is it the right decision
or the convenient decision?
Because of you,
I could never develop any ambitions.
All I did was underestimate myself!
The elders in this house
only want the respect that comes with age,
but they fail to exercise maturity!
Stop, Piu!
You're talking to your grandpa.
Where did you learn
to talk to your elders in this manner?
From your mother
or from that new boyfriend of yours?
Definitely not from you! You're never
at home to teach me anything!
I don't believe this, Piu.
I never even dreamed
that my daughter whom I
love the most in the world
would ever talk to me like this.
That boy was right.
You can definitely become a lawyer.
But not in our firm.
Your actions say just one thing, Papa.
That you only love yourself.
You have given me everything in life.
This home, a new car every year,
fancy clothes, the world's best education.
But not a father's love.
I really wish that
someday you'll be capable of love.
For the sake of your new child
and your new wife.
I will live with Mama!
Congratulations… for the next 24 years!
Mother.
P, look, I know
everything looks difficult today.
But in time,
everything will start to be okay again.
Don't worry.
And we promise,
we won't let anyone know anything.
We are with you.
Pia, Rudra just called.
Her Highness Priyanjali has called for us.
We'll have to leave today.
We'll leave, okay?
Call us if you need anything.
We love you so much.
- Come on. Bye, Aunty.
- Bye. Bye, my dear.
I had no idea
that you were blaming yourself
for the fights between Rajat and myself.
It's not your fault at all.
I made many mistakes.
I only thought about
what people would think.
How to maintain our status in society,
how to keep people happy…
I never thought about myself.
What do I want?
What are my ambitions? What are my goals?
I had no control over my life.
That's why I used to control yours.
But today, I know
that your ambitions, your goals,
and your dreams
are yours alone.
Whatever you do, do it for yourself.
Dear, you will find it difficult
for a while.
Your life will change a lot.
But Mama's there.
If you make a mistake in life,
start again with courage.
Never lose hope.
I have full faith in you.
I know you're very strong.
I'll make everything all right.
I'll fix it for us.
I love you the most.
You know that.
I got two missed calls
and a message from Arjun.
Arjun doesn't know
that Pia broke her phone.
But we cannot tell him anything.
We have just promised Pia.
Yes, this would be best.
- We've got this. We have to win this.
- But, guys, where is Pia?
Boys, leave.
The number you have called
is currently switched off.
It's been a month since we opened
our summer palace to tourists.
The whole day is filled with
photo sessions and singing and dancing.
But who would have thought that
even after the king's passing,
there would continue to be
so much gaiety in this palace?
Everybody assumes that
there's no life without a man.
But the truth is the exact opposite.
Your life has just begun.
Focus on yourself, Neelu.
Absolutely agree.
Neelu Aunty, you are one of
the strongest women I know.
And you've raised a strong one too.
Grandma, I was thinking,
why not have Neelu Aunty take over
the palace renovations?
- Me?
- You're an interior designer.
And you've designed all the offices
and the home of Jaisingh & Sons
so beautifully.
It will truly be our honour.
Come on, bro.
Guys, have y'all been to Bombay?
Go.
Of course…
Forgetting all shame,
staring into each other's eyes,
just dance, dance, dance.
Wasn't Pia with Rudra last night?
She must be quite tired.
Long, long night they must have had.
Come on, man. Just leave him alone.
Let's go.
The royal family
thanks the press and guests
for joining us today for the palace tour.
We will proceed towards the Hawa Mahal.
So, what are your plans for the future?
Still focused on fashion design
or something new.
I have decided to study law.
Law? Really?
I want to become a bigger lawyer
than Papa and Grandpa.
If Jaisingh & Sons won't accept me,
I'll create Pia Jaisingh & Co.
You've grown up.
I've had to.
Life forced me to start adulting.
Well, adulting suits you.
Pia, if you need anything, I'm right here.
Not help, I'm offering support.
Thank you.
Hi.
- Good evening, everyone…
- Phone.
…and welcome to the International
Debate Championship 2024…
Arjun? Phone.
…In Mumbai for the first time ever.
All participants are requested to take
their respective seats, and let's begin.
Guys, listen.
When they are talking,
you listen carefully. Okay?
- Yes, sir.
- All the best.
- Thank you, sir.
This is for you.
I heard about your phone.
Rudra, I can't accept this gift.
Don't call it a gift.
It's a token of love from Grandma.
She thought if I handed it over,
you'd like it better.
Don't worry,
you will not miss your old phone.
Thanks to Neelu Aunty, your sim card
and all your contacts have been loaded.
It's as good as… old?
Thank you so much again, Rudra.
That's honestly
very sweet of Her Highness.
So much has happened since last night
that I completely forgot about my phone.
Actually, I should have been
in Mumbai today.
For the debate competition.
I'm so sorry, I need to call Arjun.
And therefore, democracy ensures
innovation and progress.
So, what does the opposition
have to say about this?
Yeah.
I feel that…
We feel that…
You are flirting with me, Mehta.
Last night, Pia was with Rudra. Right?
She must be quite tired.
Long, long night they must have had!
Come on man, just leave him alone.
And that was the buzzer. Time is up.
And the winning team
is Ramneek Botswald and contingent.
Second place, Arjun Mehta and contingent.
Congratulations!
Oh, shit.
I haven't told Arjun anything yet.
Switch on, switch on, switch on.
PRATHANA ARORA:
WHY DIDN'T YOU COME TO BOMBAY?
DEV KAKKAR: PIA, WE CAME SECOND,
PLS TALK TO ARJUN…
RHEA: PIA, WHAT IS THIS?
CALL US WHEN U CAN!
SAHIRA: WHAT ARE THESE PHOTOS?
ARE YOU OKAY?
Pia is the one
who has won the real trophy.
Look at this!
Pia Jaisingh and Rudra Pratap Singh.
A fairy tale come true!
What do you guys think?
Nice, right? I like that couple.
What happened?
You were talking a lot earlier, Mehta.
Why are you quiet now?
Who's the massive little dimwit
of a clown now?
- You'll do nothing!
- Arjun!
You came second here
and are second there too.
- Arjun?
- What?!
I lost, Ma.
I got distracted.
For the first time in my life,
And look what happened.
Why did we change schools, Ma?
I was better off in that boys' school.
Arjun…
Pia, everyone's waiting
for you back there.
What happened?
Your problem is my problem.
You don't worry. I'll figure it out.
You won't see these photos anymore.
Arjun!
Just wait two minutes.
Just listen to me, please.
Arjun, I know you're upset
that I couldn't come.
Why are you reacting
without knowing the full story?
Arjun, please, you don't know
what happened on Diwali night!
Enough, Pia! Shut up!
I've had enough of your bullshit!
Your dad was right.
You don't have the focus to be a lawyer.
I'm such an idiot that I believed in you.
I prioritised you. But what did you do?
You switched off your phone
and disappeared.
You ghosted me, man!
Arjun, that's not the case!
Please, just one moment...
Give your bullshit to Rudra, Pia!
Spare me, please!
Rudra is just a family friend!
Really? Family friend?
It doesn't look like that in the photos.
Are you fake-dating him too?
Like you did with me?
- Fake-dating?
- What?
Do you give him money every week?
Or does he pay you?
That's right, everyone!
I got 25,000 every week
to pretend to be her boyfriend.
- What?
- Oh fuck! Oh my God!
Arjun, what are you doing?
Everybody's watching.
Show a little respect.
What respect, Veer?
She hired me because
she wanted validation from you all.
You and your great gang of friends,
where everything is fake!
I knew it.
There could never be anything
between this bloody ape and Pia.
Everything's fake.
Easy.
You want to teach me
about real and fake? Bloody faker!
Ayaan used to keep messaging Pia.
To this day,
he continues to message other girls.
He's a cheater and a repeat offender.
In fact, let's recap all of this.
Pia hired me only because
she wanted to win back
her thin-skinned, ultra-sensitive BFFs.
And most importantly,
so that this fakester Ayaan
would stop sniffing around her behind.
Just buzz off, man!
You had to hire a fake boyfriend, Pia!
But fake friends, you got for free.
Sahira, why have you blocked me?
How are you believing Arjun?
He is lying. You're...
Enough, Ayaan! What are you doing?
I'm emotional, yes,
but I'm not a pushover
you can exploit whenever you want.
You were never worthy of my love.
Why did you reject my application?
Because I stood second
in the debate championship?
Not at all, Arjun.
I'd like you to rewrite your essay
and resubmit it.
We can't submit your application
with such an aggressive essay.
I hope you understand.
No, ma'am. I am the way I am.
I don't want to change myself for others.
I also have self-respect.
Arjun, if you make a few changes
in your essay and resend it,
you won't lose any self-respect.
Okay? If you don't change yourself,
life will ensure it changes you.
Trust me on that.
Arjun, don't ruin such a promising life
over such a small issue.
YOLO.
"You only live once."
- That was absolutely right, ma'am.
- Exactly.
That was right.
Arjun,
you were right,
and I was the biggest idiot.
I did hire a fake boyfriend.
But then I developed real expectations
from this fake boyfriend.
Speaking of which,
you're an incredible actor.
You really had everyone convinced
that you were my boyfriend.
Including me.
You turned out to be a red flag too
after all.
You know, I'm glad this happened.
Imagine being stuck with someone
who can neither trust nor communicate,
and who is so lacking in patience
that he gives no one a chance
to explain their side of things.
This time, let's make a deal
never to meet again.
On this, I'll give you a 100% discount.
And there will be nothing fake about it.
Arjun,
you should understand the difference
between ego and self-respect.
What you did was wrong.
It's not about ego or about self-respect.
One second.
How do you know?
Did you read my letter?
Are there no boundaries in this house?!
That's not cool, Ma!
What's not cool, Arjun,
is that you broke Pia's heart.
What's not cool
is that you broke her trust.
What's not cool is that you insulted Pia.
What's not cool
is that you never share your emotions!
is that your generation assumes
that by sharing
your feelings and emotions,
you're exposing a weakness!
- Ma, take my side at least once!
- I'm always on your side, Arjun!
What are you saying?!
I mean, clearly not!
Why did you read my letter?!
That's not cool! It's my private stuff!
What privacy
between a mother and child, Arjun?!
- There should be!
- Hey!
- I deserve to have my own personal space!
- Time out!
Arjun! Come out. Now!
Are you okay?
I'll talk to him.
Ice cream along with falooda. What fun!
Isn't tomorrow the last day of school?
Bonfire Night?
I hope you're going.
You're exactly like me.
So much anger.
And nobody to vent it on.
Come on, take it all out on me.
I never had such an opportunity
with my Papa.
I used to be afraid of him.
I wish just once,
he'd let me expend my anger completely.
ICE CREAM WITH FALOODA
Can I tell you something?
I hated falooda.
But your mother and I
used to go for a walk after work.
And we would share one ice cream.
Let me guess. She loved falooda.
But Papa, you made
so many sacrifices for Ma...
Love.
A thing that once irritated you the most?
The same thing slowly turns into
your favourite thing,
and you never even realize.
Tell me the truth.
Have you broken up with Pia?
Is that why she doesn't visit us anymore?
What was between Pia and you,
I thought it wasn't a good thing at first.
We're all… so different, man.
But then I saw
that being dissimilar
can also be very beautiful.
Look, everyone knows the story
of Romeo and Juliet. Right?
But do you know
who Romeo's first love was?
Rosaline.
And if Rosaline
hadn't come into Romeo's life,
then Romeo wouldn't have found Juliet.
One can fall in love twice.
Maybe thrice too.
Sometimes,
people fall in love multiple times.
But you find your Juliet
only once in a lifetime.
Now, it's up to you
to decide if Pia is your Rosaline,
whom you can let go,
or your Juliet,
whom you would like to fight for.
Live for.
Die for.
Let's go.
I blew it, Papa.
I spoke to her so rudely.
She doesn't want to see my face
ever again.
I've made a big mistake, Papa.
It wasn't a mistake.
This is what is known as innocence.
And a love that has no room
for little acts of innocence…
Where's the fun in that?
It's like having ice cream
without falooda.
Cheesy.
Made you smile.
So, one has to prioritise relationships.
One has to work on them every day.
There's a vision board for them too.
So don't forget this department
while you're busy
with your work and achievements.
I love you, Dad.
Oh, my dear. It's going to be all right.
Shit! I forgot to pack
some ice cream for your mom.
She'll be angry.
Arjun!
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm so proud of you. I love you.
What did I not tell you?
Arjun! You've been accepted
to UK's top university!
And they're giving you a full scholarship
too, in sports. I-T-T-T-D.
IIT Delhi?
Arjun! I-T-T-T-D.
"It's the time to disco."
Wow, champ!
When did you resubmit the essay?
- I'm wondering the same thing.
- Pia submitted it for him.
And I'm so happy, Arjun,
that you took my advice seriously
and wrote the essay again. Good boy.
Did Pia also get her admission in the UK?
Yes. But unfortunately,
she's not accepting it.
I mean, Pia is not going
to the UK anymore.
Why?
Because of her family situation.
I'm so sorry. I thought you all knew.
Pia's parents are getting divorced,
and that's why she's changed her mind.
Arjun…
The number you have called
is currently switched off.
The number you have called is currently…
Sahira, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't hang up.. don't hang up!
It's the feelings in the heart
Little failings that make us part
In love there's bound to be
Innocence
Wow!
P, this one's for you.
I know there are a lot of red flags in me.
But today, I haven't brought
any argument, any theory,
or any justification to you.
I'm here by myself, your green flag,
to ask your forgiveness.
You really hurt me, Arjun.
I really thought that you were different.
But you turned out to be
just like all the other boys.
- No, Pia, please. Pia, I'm sorry.
- Arjun, let me go.
Pia, wait. Please listen...
- Arjun please, just let me go!
- No, Pia, please!
- Arjun, please!
- No!
Not today.
I was naive
to let go of what was between us
so easily.
I could never understand
that though our dating was fake,
what I was feeling for you
was not fake.
What was fake was that
I hid my true feelings from you up to now.
I could not say that I felt really jealous
when I saw those photos of you with Rudra.
How can I know
whether all this is real or fake?
Right now, at this moment,
I could leave everything for you
in a second.
And I won't regret it.
ThePia Jaisingh, you are my Juliet.
Love is like magic.
And you are magic.
The magic that will leave me hollow
if I lose it.
The magic that I've somehow lived without
this far, but no more.
I guess what I'm trying to say,
rather badly,
is that, Pia Jaisingh…
I love you.
And however stupid,
idiotic, and annoying I am…
There's nothing fake in this.
So, please take me back.
Take you back?
When were you ever mine,
that I should take you back?
You have tears in your eyes,
and still so much attitude?
Then just please agree that
you feel something.
I do feel a lot, Arjun!
It's not like I'm an AI robot!
Then say it, before my knees give way.
Say what?!
What a big drama king you are?!
You know very well how I feel about you.
You also know
what all of this means to me.
You really hurt me, Arjun.
I thought I would never
be able to forgive you.
Never speak to you again.
But when I see you, I forget everything.
I'm not different.
I'm just different when I'm with you.
I guess what I'm trying to say,
rather badly…
Is that I love you, Arjun Mehta.
However, stupid, idiotic,
and annoying I am,
you are the same.
Whatever and however I am,
One second.
Now it feels normal.
So that's how I learned
that sometimes, even the wrong reasons
lead you to finding the right person.
And when the right person
is really by your side,
then adulting
doesn't feel so impossible after all.
What now?
I've borrowed Arjun's dreams
and he's borrowed mine.
He's going to London
and I'm going to law school here.
There'll be 6,000 kilometres
separating us.
I hope we do it right.
Just like Arjun's papa said,
there's a vision board
for relationships too.
If you want it, you have to work for it.
But you should also allow room
for a few mistakes.
After all,
a love that has no room
for little acts of innocence…
Where's the fun in that?
HERE'S THE RECIPE, SON. NOW YOU DON'T NEED
TO COME HOME EVEN ON THE WEEKENDS.
BC = BOYS, LET'S GO!!
Subtitle translation by: Neena Kiss